adata-group.com 2012-12-14

# ADATA Technology - the leading provider of DRAM modules, USB Flash drive, External Storage, Memory cards, solid state drives, cloud computing and data storage solutions.

ADATA is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website, and of all customers who purchase our products. "ADATA" refers to ADATA Technology Co., Ltd. and its subsidiaries and affiliates.   
The Privacy Policy (the "Policy") below is intended to aid understanding of what personal information is collected and how that information is used. By using ADATA’s website and/or by submitting personal information to ADATA, you express your agreement to the processing of your personal information in the manner provided in the Policy. If you do not agree with the Policy, please cease using ADATA’s website or providing ADATA with your personal information. 

**Information Gathered on ADATA Website**

ADATA’s website, email messages, and online advertisements may use "cookies" and other tracking technologies. The non-personal information acquired by these technologies is used to monitor and improve the website presence and user experience. Some information is recorded automatically and stored in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, internet service provider, referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, as well as to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. ADATA may use this information in our marketing and advertising services

 **  
Information Gathered from Product Registration**

Our purpose in collecting personal information from our users is to help ADATA provide a service the user has requested, and/or learn about end-users and potential end-users of our products so that we can better tailor product features, performance and support, and offer additional information and opportunities. Personal Information collected includes your name, address, phone number, details of purchases, and other information than can be used to identify you and is voluntarily submitted to ADATA by you. 

**Security of Personal Information**

All personal information collected by ADATA is stored securely, and ADATA will not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties unless otherwise stated below.   
A.ADATA may share your personal information if we have your consent to do so.  
B.ADATA may be obligated to disclose your personal information to certain authorities or other third parties pursuant to mandatory law or court order(s). ADATA may also disclose or otherwise process your personal information in accordance with applicable law to defend ADATA’s legitimate interests, for example, in civil, criminal or administrative procedures.

**Your Rights**

In case you wish to know what personal information we hold about you, or you wish to revise or delete any personal information, or if you wish us to cease sending you promotional or direct marketing materials, you may contact us at AskADATA@adata.com.tw. However, ADATA may need to identify you and to ask for additional information in order to be able to fulfill such requests. Please also note that applicable law may contain restrictions and other provisions that relate to your above rights. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

ADATA reserves the right to amend the Policy as it deems it is necessary. Any changes in the Policy will be announced on the ADATA website. Your use of ADATA’s website after such change confirms your agreement to any revised Policy.
